漫威出品
捍卫者联盟
第一季  第五集
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     捍卫者联草
翻译     克里斯
校对     奶卫联盟
时间轴     今  大葱
后期     拳拳和马律师的8T
总监     奶卫联盟
人人影视Pro
人人影视官方唯一APP
在线观看，离线缓存，百度云
app.YYeTs.com
官方网站下载 : 人人影视Pro
最新海外影视剧下载
人人影视Pro
人人官方唯一APP
在线观看，离线缓存
这是谁
Who's this?
-她真烦人  -可不是吗
- She's annoying. - Tell me about it.
亚历山德拉去哪了
Where's Alexandra?
趴下
Get down!
老兄  放开我
Dude, get off me.
派对开始了
Now it's a goddamn party.
-这些人是谁  -他们想抓丹尼
- Who are these people? - They want Danny.
我们要活的
We want him alive.
该死
Oh, shit.
通力合作  我们就能活着出去
We work together, we walk out of here alive.
不
No!
等等  我只想和你谈谈
Wait, I just wanna talk to you.
马特在哪  他在想什么
Where's Matt? What's he thinking?
他没动脑子  专心点
He's not. Stay with me!
这不是真正的你
This is not who you are.
我了解你
I know you.
你死了
You died.
我把你抱在怀里
I held you in my arms.
我把你埋了  艾丽卡
I buried you, Elektra!
艾丽卡
Elektra.
那是你的名字
That's your name.
艾丽卡
Elektra.
他们对你做了什么
What have they done to you?
你在干什么
What are you doing?
我能帮你  艾丽卡
I can help you, Elektra!
他们说你无坚不摧
They say you can't be broken.
我们走着瞧吧
We'll see about that.
卢克
Luke!
快抓住他
Get him, now.
我们走  孩子
Let's go, kid.
-卢克呢  -他们抓走了他
- Where's Luke? - They took him.
-更多人在后面  -马上不会了
- More comin'. - Not for long.
我们走
Let's go.
这边来  伙计们
Get over here, guys!
闻着像屎一样
Smells like shit.
只有这一条路撤退
It's our only way out.
他们去哪了  黑空呢
Where did they go? And where's the Black Sky?
这该问我们的领袖
That's a question for our leader.
丹尼
Danny!
-很高兴见到你  -你去哪了
- Man, am I glad to see you. - Where've you been?
我会解释一切  不过有客人来了
I'll explain everything, but first... we have company.
客人
Company?
我说过会带他回来
I said I'd bring him back.
发生了什么
What happened?
手和会袭击了我们  抓走了卢克
The Hand attacked us. They took Luke.
你怎么确定他们没跟你到这
How do you know they didn't follow you here?
没人跟踪我们
We're clear.
-什么  -我们所到之处不会安全太久
- What? - No place we land will stay safe for long.
-我们不能一直逃避  -我不要跑
- We can't keep running forever. - I'm not running, period.
我们公司在附近有一栋楼
My company owns a building not far from here.
我们不需要藏身处  我们需要了结这件事
We don't need another hideout. We just need for this to be over.
-你想得太简单了  -是吗
- You're oversimplifying it. - Oh, am I?
也许只有我没拿这件事追求一时的刺激
Or am I the only one of us who isn't in this for a cheap thrill?
-杰西卡  -上次我们确实有个计划
- Jessica. - And the last time we did have a plan,
这家伙却丢下我们  跑去打那个穿紧身衣的妞
but this one left us to go fight that chick in the spandex.
对  就像中城圈那次一样
Yeah. Just like he did in Midland Circle.
我犯了个错误  我以为
I made a mistake. I thought...
卢克
Luke?
-发生什么了  -你还好吗
- What happened? - Are you okay?
我没事
I'm fine.
事实上  我好极了
Actually, I'm, uh... I'm better than fine.
我抓住了一个他们的人
I got one of theirs.
你武艺精湛了  孩子
You're skilled, my child.
当你战斗时  很明显
It's clear, watching you fight,
你会运用的招数比别人一辈子会的都多
that you know much more than anyone can learn in a single life.
这是在夸你
That's a compliment.
他们也对我说过同样的话
They've said the same thing about me.
你把我训练得很好
You've trained me well.
我曾有个女儿
I had a daughter once.
是在第一轮生命的时候
This was in my first life.
那时我还没去昆仑朝圣
Before I made the pilgrimage to K'un-Lun.
还不知道圣物
Before I learned of the substance.
也还没建立这个组织
And before I started the organization.
她很聪明  和善
And she was intelligent, kind...
但在我战胜死亡前  它却夺走了她
And death took her from me before I learned how to defeat it.
在悲痛中  别人告诉我
In my grief, people told me
她太单纯美好  不该来这个世界
that she was too good for this world.
我不相信他们
I didn't believe them.
但他们说的也不全错
But there was some truth in what they said.
她不是个勇士
She wasn't a warrior.
她不像你我一样
She wasn't like you and me.
现在我知道了
And now I know...
我压根不该养育她
I was never meant to raise her.
我该养育的是黑空
I was meant to raise the Black Sky.
我很感激有你
I'm grateful for you.
起死回生时  你没有选择
You had no choice in returning from death.
我理解
I realize that.
但我希望你明白
But I hope you understand
作为一件抵御敌人的武器
that this is the life you were chosen to lead,
这才是你的宿命
as a weapon against our enemies.
如果你不能完成这个使命
If you do not fulfill that role...
你对手和会就没有价值
you're of no use to the Hand.
对我也是
Or to me.
当然
Of course not.
有新消息
I have news.
索旺达被抓走了
Sowande has been taken.
被谁
By whom?
应该是铁拳和他的盟友
We can only assume it was the Iron Fist and his allies.
这些年来
Over the years,
我们五个每次都能化险为夷
the five of us have escaped every manner of danger and death.
他会回来找我们的
He will find his way back to us.
与此同时  通知其他人
In the meantime, tell the others
我们南美的援军很快就到
that our reinforcement from South America will be arriving soon.
与之合作  我们将扩大对铁拳的搜寻
And together, we will expand our search for the Iron Fist.
好的
I will.
还有件事必须讨论一下
There is something else we must discuss.
换个时间
Later.
好的
As you wish.
你觉得他还会晕多久
How long do you think he'll be out?
-没多久了  -你怎么知道
- Not much longer. - How do you know?
因为我会这样
Because this is happening.
你来纽约做什么
What are you doing in New York?
无论如何我也不会背叛自己的盟友
There's nothing you can do to make me betray my own.
我愿接受挑战
I'm up for the challenge.
别麻烦了  五指都是在昆仑选中的
Don't bother. The fingers were cast out of K'un-Lun.
这意味着他是跟随养育铁拳的僧人训练的
Which means he trained with the same monks that raised him.
-所以呢  -让我们接受严苛考验
- So? - Put us through brutal trials.
这叫戒律
It's called discipline.
也就意味着他不会松口
It means he won't crack.
不能靠武力
Not by force.
你对手和会的力量一无所知
You know nothing of the power of the Hand.
你就是落入深井的老鼠
You are mice who fell into a well.
相信我  你会淹死的
Believe me, this will drown you.
你想把我的城市怎么样
What do you want with our city?
你的城市
Your city?
这地方属于手和会  一直如此
This place belongs to the Hand. It always has.
"一直"是什么意思
What do you mean, "Always"?
我查到他们最早成立于1820年
I traced it back to 1820.
-就这样  -你们为什么想抓丹尼·兰德
- That's all? - Why do you want Danny Rand?
你永远不会为你们效力
Nothing you can do can make me serve you.
-你明白吗  -我明白吗
- Do you understand? - Do I understand?
你是最蠢的一任铁拳了
You are the dumbest Iron Fist yet.
告诉我你们为什么要抓我
Tell me what you want with me.
我们要的是拳
We want the Fist.
你毫无价值
You are nothing.
丹尼·兰德辜负了整座城市
Danny Rand failed an entire city.
他本该誓死保护这个地方
The place he was sworn to protect.
正如那个无坚不摧的家伙任由那个男孩死在监狱
The same way the unbreakable one let that boy die in a jail cell.
害怕而又孤单
Afraid and alone.
正如那个女人没能救到那个建筑师
The same way the woman couldn't save the architect.
哪里出错了
What's wrong?
我也像他之前那样  控制了你的大脑吗
Have I gotten in your head the same way he did long ago?
还有你曾爱的那些人
What about the ones you still love?
你离开之后  他们会怎么样
What will become of them once you are gone?
-还有谁因你而死  -你在说什么
- Who else must die because of you? - What are you talking about?
那个护士  广播台的那个女人
The nurse. The woman on the radio.
接下来就轮到她们
They'll come for them next.
还有多少老鼠要陪你们淹死
How many mice must drown with you?
他话太多了
He talked too much.
-克莱尔  马上穿好衣服  -怎么了
- Claire, I need you to get dressed. - What's going on?
-你妈还在吗  -不  她跟阿姨回新泽西了
- Is your mom still here? - No, she's in Jersey with my tía.
好的  我们得赶紧走
Okay. We need to go now.
丹尼和科琳正在楼下帮我们盯梢
Danny and Colleen are downstairs keeping an eye out for us.
盯梢
Keeping an eye out?
到车里我再跟你解释
I'll explain everything in the car.
你跟手和会打了一架
You took the fight to the Hand.
开始很顺利  但现在我们都身处险境
It went well at first, but now we're all in danger.
我真恨自己总能说对
I hate being right all the time.
这种局面只会持续几天
It'll only be for a couple days.
你打算告诉我到底是怎么回事吗
So, are you gonna tell me what this is all about?
目前来说  你知道的越少越好
At this point, the less you know, the better.
你确定吗
Are you sure about that?
几天前  还是我把你介绍给丹尼·兰德
A couple days ago, I'm the one who introduced you to Danny Rand.
对  可你还告诉我专注于自己
Yeah, and you also told me to focus on myself.
我有点希望当时听了你的话
Part of me wishes I had listened.
-对不起  -为什么
- I'm sorry. - For what?
这一切
All of it.
我从没想把我的麻烦变成你的麻烦
I never meant to make my trouble your trouble.
我敢肯定你的麻烦现在就是我的麻烦了
Pretty sure your trouble is my trouble now.
那个失明的老头说...
The old blind guy kept saying that...
他必须赶在他们之前找到你
he needed to get to you before they did.
因为手和会不想杀掉我
It's because the Hand doesn't wanna kill me.
他们想让我活着
They want me alive.
他告诉你原因了吗
He tell you why?
没
No.
说实话  我觉得他也不知道
To be honest, I don't think he knows, either.
那你为什么听他的
Then why are you listening to him?
你什么意思
What do you mean?
你为什么要听他们说的话  丹尼
Why are you listening to any of them, Danny?
我之前说我们应该找到其他人  我不是说...
When I said that we should find others, I did not mean...
这不是他们的战斗  是我们的
This is not their fight, it's ours,
留着他们是个负担
and keeping them around is a liability.
你还没见过他们的能耐
You haven't really seen what they can do.
这不是重点
That's not the point.
快
Quick.
你好  科琳
Hello, Colleen.
老师
Sensei.
你看上去不错
You look well.
你应该死了啊
You're supposed to be dead.
我试过死亡  没成功
I tried death. It didn't take.
退下
Stand down.
她是老朋友
She's an old friend.
我们远算不上朋友
We are far from friends.
我可不会这么说
I wouldn't say that.
等你比划够了  我想谈谈
When you're done with that, I'd like to talk.
没什么好谈的
There's nothing left to talk about.
感觉就像命运又让我们重聚了  不是吗
It feels as if fate has brought us back together, doesn't it?
你想对丹尼怎么样
What do you want with Danny?
他们派我来抓他  没错
They sent me for him, yes.
但我是为你而来
But I came for you.
胡说  你说我不够优秀  不能加入手和会
Bullshit. You told me I wasn't good enough for the Hand.
那是策略  激发你的怒气
It was a strategy. To bring out your anger.
故意让你犯错
To cause you to make a mistake.
我们现在又有一次机会完成我们的事业
We have a second chance to finish what we started.
给我洗脑
Brainwashing me?
洗脑
Brainwashing?
你在我的训练下进步神速
You flourished under my training.
成为了你注定要成为的斗士
Became the fighter you were meant to be.
是你想让我成为的斗士
The fighter you wanted me to be.
你只不过需要我
The one you needed
帮你摆脱你摊上的那些烂事
for whatever horrible shit you're trying to get away with.
加入我  科琳
Join me, Colleen.
这次我会告诉你一切
This time I'll tell you everything.
我料到会有这次重聚
I anticipated this reunion.
我可没有
I didn't.
我不会停下的  你夺走了我的生活[生命]
I'll never stop. You took my life from me.
不  我没有  科琳  还没有
No, I haven't, Colleen. Not yet.
多希望事情不必演变至此
I wish it could end another way.
我们上次见到那哥们时  他死透了吧
That dude was for sure dead last time we saw him, right?
-没错  -好  就确认一下
- Oh, yeah. - Okay, just checking.
还记得我们上一次对决吗  博徒
Remember the last time we faced off, Bakuto?
我记得  兰德先生  我很期待再次交手
I do, Mr. Rand. And I look forward to doing it again.
你不该期待的
You really shouldn't.
我听说你交了些朋友
I heard you'd made some friends.
聪明  毕竟她从不相信自己的使命
Smart move, considering she never believed in her purpose,
而你还没有发觉你的使命
and you've yet to discover yours.
很快  铁拳
Soon, Iron Fist.
你就会知道你的命运
You'll learn your destiny
远不止他们在昆仑告诉你的那些
is much more than what they told you in K'un-Lun.
我们得找个地方安置她
We need to get her someplace now.
已经后半夜了
It's after midnight.
如果事情不紧急  我也不会来
I wouldn't be here if it wasn't important.
你得再说详细一点
I'm gonna need a little more than that.
是手和会
It's the Hand.
他们之前来找过你  我不能让这种事再发生
They came for you before, Karen. I can't let that happen again.
我不相信
I don't believe this.
我知道  他们回到纽约了
I know. They're back in New York,
-我...  -不  不是他们
- and I-- - No, no, it's not them.
是你
You.
你是说你又要重操旧业了
This is how you tell me that you're doing it again?
因为你就这个意思  你又要惩恶扬善了
'Cause that's what you're saying. You're going out as him.
不  事实上
Uh, no, actually.
暂时还没有
Uh, well... not yet.
好吧  但你说过你不怀念那种感觉
All right, but you told me you didn't miss it--
我知道  我们不必谈这个话题
I know what I said. We don't have to have this conversation.
告诉我吧  求你了  马特  开口吧
Just talk to me. Please, Matt. Just... just tell me.
我又要重操旧业了
I'm doing it again.
如果我不这样做  很多人会死
Because if I don't, people will die.
不管手和会有何企图
Whatever the Hand is up to...
纽约都危在旦夕  我必须这样做
New York is in its crosshairs. I have to do this.
我知道
I know.
但我不必
But I don't.
我不需要你的保护  马特
I don't need your protection, Matt.
不管你或者夜魔侠在做什么
Whatever it is you're doing, or Daredevil is doing,
我都不参与其中了  所以
I'm not a part of it anymore. So...
可能是这样  没错
That may be the case, yeah.
不幸的是  你和夜魔侠的时间
Unfortunately, it doesn't matter
有没有瓜葛都无所谓
if you're a part of Daredevil's world or not,
因为他们也盯上了马特·默多克
because they may be coming after Matt Murdock's, too.
不好意思  你是说他们知道你的身份吗
I'm sorry, does that mean they know who you are?
我们冒不起这险
Just can't take any chances.
马特  这不是你能决定的
Matt, that isn't your call.
你能跟我走吗  低调几天
Can you please just come with me? Just lay low, a couple days.
我只要求这么多  抱歉
That's all I'm asking. I'm sorry.
好吧
Okay.
谢谢你
Thank you.
不必客气
Yeah, well, don't.
我不是为了你这样做  只是...
I'm not doing this for you. It's just...
临时自保的策略
self-preservation at this point.
你值得更好的  凯伦
You deserve better, Karen.
你也是
So do you.
-米丝蒂  -卢克
- Misty. - Luke.
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.
好吧
Okay.
怎么了
What's going on?
你知道你追捕的那些人吧  杀害科尔的那些人
You know those people you were after? The ones that killed Cole?
-嗯  -他们不会很快收手
- Yeah. - They're not stopping anytime soon.
-你怎么知道  -我...
- Well, what do you know? - It's...
说来话长  不过他们很危险
It's complicated, but they're very dangerous.
那个乱作一团的
Any chance that four-star shit-show
中餐馆是不是你的杰作
at the Chinese restaurant was your fault?
你惹了什么麻烦  卢克
What have you gotten yourself into, Luke?
告诉我
Just tell me.
我有纽约警局的所有资源  我可能知道些什么
I've got the full resources of the NYPD. I might know something.
说不定我们是同一边的
Hell, we might even be on the same side.
你知道我们是同一边的
You know we're on the same side.
就算我说了  你也不会相信
You wouldn't believe me if I told you anyway.
那我就不知道怎样帮你了
Then I don't know how I can help you.
有椅子吗
You got a chair?
搞什么
What the hell?
还有其他人
We've got more coming.
求你了  相信我
Please. Trust me.
还好吗
Okay?
嗯
Yeah.
我一直在想何时会再见到你
I was wondering when I'd see you again.
我也是
Me, too.
看来今天是见不着了
Guess it won't be today.
曾经与你并肩作战的那支军队
That army you used to fight alongside...
真纯会
The Chaste.
我曾经被他们俘虏过
They captured me once.
那是多年以前了  你都还没出生
This was years ago. Long before you were born.
我被他们关了三天
I had been captive three days
然后他们就被我的士兵围住了
when they heard my soldiers approach.
城堡一片寂静
The fortress fell silent.
大门死死锁住
The gates remained locked.
真纯会不明白对方的企图
The Chaste couldn't comprehend it.
但是外边的士兵  是在执行我的命令
But the soldiers outside, they were following my orders.
他们封死大门  不许人进出
They sealed the gates, allowed no one in or out.
第三天  你的人就开始互相反目
On the third day, your soldiers turned on each other.
第四天  饮水告竭  第六天  食物耗尽
By the fourth, they'd run out of water. By the sixth, no food.
我记得是到了第十天  他们跪着求我
I believe it was the tenth day that they knelt before me.
求我下令解围
Begging to make it stop.
如果我现在就跪下求你  蠢货
if I kneel before you right now, shithead,
你能闭嘴吗
will you shut up?
你们的计划很快就会破产
It won't be long before your plan comes apart.
那时我这把囚椅就会变成王座
Before this chair I'm in becomes a throne.
-大家都安全了  -很好
- We're getting everyone safe. - Good.
他招了什么了吗
He give you anything yet?
你以为呢
What do you think?
要是她真有闻起来那么动人
If she's as sweet as she smells,
我倒是理解你为什么不肯放手
I get why you're tore up about this one.
别把她牵扯进来
Don't bring her into this.
我护着你这么多年  就是怕你遇上这种事
All these years, this is what I've been protecting you from.
这下你的两个生活相撞了
Your two worlds colliding.
要是按你的来  我的生活就会是这样
If you had it your way, this is what my life would be.
现在你倒说得好像你是保护我
Now you're trying to spin it like you're protecting me.
-也许是我人老心软了  -才怪
- Maybe I got soft in my old age. - Doubt it.
又或许我知道前线需要什么样的人
Or maybe I know what I need on the front lines.
因为铁拳无法像你那样领导他们
'Cause the Iron Fist can't lead 'em like you can.
我可不想领导任何人  棍叟
I don't wanna lead anyone, Stick.
你这么虔诚  怎么总喜欢否认上帝
For a man who believes in God, you sure like denying
-对你的安排呢  -别用我的信仰来对付我
- He has a plan for you. - Don't use my faith against me.
那这座城市呢
And what about this city?
这座你离不开的城市
The place you can't live without.
这座造就了如今的你的城市
The place that made you what you really are.
-你要去哪  -不要
- Where are you going? - Don't...
不用你告诉我我是谁  相信我  我自己知道
You don't get to tell me who I am, all right? Trust me, I know.
我的意思是说《崔西说》前景非常好
I guess what I'm saying is I see a future for Trish Talk
在深入调查报道方面很有潜力
that dives into some more investigative reporting.
比如说这次的地震  不知道各位听没听说
This tremor stuff, for example, I don't know if you guys know,
-但是有许多听众认为...  -崔西
- but a lot of our listeners are having a... - Trish.
杰西
Jess?
-我有话和她说  -什么
- I need her for a minute. - What?
-来吧快走  会议结束了  -失陪一下
- Come on, we gotta go. Meeting's over. - Excuse me for one second.
-你没事吧  -有事
- Are you okay? - No.
你还记得我接的建筑师的案子吗  炸药案
You know that case I took? The architect? The C-4?
出了大事了  你可能有危险
Well, it went south fast, and you may be in danger.
我  没关系  我不能丢下这些人
Me? It doesn't matter. I can't just leave those people.
他们离我们远点更安全  相信我
They are safer far away from us. Trust me.
我知道你不爽  但我得送你去安全的地方
I know it's annoying, but I gotta get you to a safe place fast.
见鬼
Shit.
去楼梯井  快
Stairwell. Go.
天啊杰西  我说你应该回去上班
Jesus Jess! When I said I thought you should get back to work,
我可不是指...
I didn't mean you should go...
杰西  杰西
Jess! Jess!
疼死了
That hurt so much.
不会吧
No way.
还是围巾更好看
The scarf looked better.
-小耳朵不错  -这是角
- Nice ears. - They're horns.
没想到这一天会这么过
Not how I imagined my day looking.
也许我就该待在这里
Maybe this is exactly where I'm supposed to be.
什么意思
What do you mean?
躲在这里
Hidden here.
远离前线
Away from the action.
被落在后面
Left behind.
-我都糊涂了  -他之前的话是错的
- I don't even know anymore. - He was wrong back there.
他不该说你弱
About your being weak.
如果你在那样环境下长大
When you're raised in something like that...
如果你做人的基础都是别人所塑造出来的...
when they've formed the foundation for who you are...
逃走就好像是
breaking away is, like...
我感觉我迷失了
I feel lost.
我也没想到我会承认这一点  但是
I can't believe I'm admitting this, but...
我最想要的
all I want...
就是一个牢固的点
is something stable.
能让我依靠
Something I can hold on to.
你这话真是有意思
Funny you should say that.
因为我了解你  了解丹尼
Because I know you. I know Danny.
我也知道与手和会的战斗
I know this fight with the Hand.
而在我看来
And where I'm standing...
你就是那个基础
you are the foundation.
你还好吧
So how are you holding up?
你知道杰西卡认识夜魔侠吗
Did you know Jessica knows Daredevil?
-什么  那个紧身衣男  -对
- What? The costume guy? - Yeah.
有人攻击了我们
And some guy attacked us.
我认为和地震有关
I think it's connected to the tremors.
肯定是有关系的  对吧
I mean, it has to be, right?
是啊  可能吧
Yeah, um, maybe.
你想喝一杯吗
Do you want one?
-我  还是算了  -聪明
- Uh, I'm... I'm okay. - Smart.
她是谁
Who's she?
记者
Reporter.
她是来采访的吗
Think she's here to write a story?
看着不像
Doesn't look like it.
你也来了
You, too?
太好了
Jesus!
我的天啊  见到你真是太高兴了
Oh, my God, am I glad to see you.
我也很高兴
I'm glad to see you.
说真的  能从取证会脱身我也挺高兴
Gotta be honest, I'm glad to have a break from depositions.
-是啊  -怎么个情况
- Yeah. - What's the story?
马特没告诉你吗
Matt didn't tell you?
马特什么都不告诉我
Matt doesn't tell me anything.
又来了
It's happening again.
我知道  我也试过分散他的注意力
I know. I tried to steer him away.
是啊  我也是
Yeah, me too.
看来还是不够
And it still wasn't enough.
说来可笑
Funny.
要不是我了解他
If I didn't know any better,
我都会以为他是想告诉我们什么
I'd think he's trying to tell us something.
-是啊  -好了  大家听好
- Yeah. - All right, listen up, everybody.
我知道各位都不想来这里
I know you don't wanna be here,
但似乎你们都认识一些
but it seems that you are all of interest
非常强大又非常危险的人
to some pretty powerful and dangerous people.
现在为了保护你们  我需要各位的配合
Now, to protect you, I need your cooperation.
大家先在这里等着  有情况会来通知的
Sit tight for now. We'll have more answers soon.
但愿吧
Hopefully.
科琳·温
Colleen Wing?
我在
Yeah. Yeah.
我听我警员说从你那没收了些不寻常的东西
I'm told my uniforms confiscated something unusual from you.
-那是武士刀  传承了...  -很诡异
- It's a katana. It was passed down... - It's weird.
好吧
Okay.
我不需要在这待着  我能保护自己
Look, I don't need to be here. I can defend myself.
你来的时候一身血  你确定吗
You came in here pretty bloody. Are you sure about that?
是
Yeah.
我确定
Yeah, I am.
你们在对抗的这些人  能告诉我什么吗
What can you tell me about these people that you're fighting?
不能
Nothing.
我告诉你越多  你就越危险
The more I tell you, the more danger I put you in.
这句话我都有点听恶心了
I'm getting pretty sick of people telling me that.
是真的
It's true.
不然我们为什么要来这
Why else would we be here?
我来是因为我是警察
I'm here 'cause I'm a cop.
相信我  他们才不管你是谁
Trust me, they don't give a shit.
以防万一
Just in case.
谢谢
Thanks.
我们现在都不讲话了吗
Are we no longer on speaking terms?
只要我们还是这个组织的一员
As long as we're in this organization,
只要我们还活着
as long as we are alive,
我们就一定是队友
we will be on the same side.
你还记得那是什么样吗
Do you remember what it looks like?
回归那里的唯一途径
The only way we return to it
就是控制住铁拳
is if we secure the Iron Fist.
我就是为这个来的
Oh, that is why I am here.
但你先去找了科琳·温
But the first person you sought out was Colleen Wing.
是  那是分配给我的任务
Hmm, yes, that was our assignment.
她也许能引领我们找到铁拳
She could lead us to the Iron Fist.
-她也做到了  其实  -以及他的盟友
- And she did. In fact... - Along with his allies.
这次没那么简单了
It is not as simple this time.
或者是你不愿意承认
Or you are not as committed.
每当事情牵涉到你的旧徒
Your judgment has always been clouded
你的判断就总会出问题
when it comes to your old disciples.
我不弄瞎我的门徒
Just because I don't blind my disciples,
并不意味着他们就是我的弱点
doesn't mean I'm made weak by them.
-很高兴见到您  -省省吧
- It's good to see you. - Save it.
-有麻烦了  -我们知道  也打算去纠正
- We have a situation. - We know, and we plan to correct it.
我们稍后再讨论你
We will discuss your failure
没能搞到谈判筹码的无能
to acquire a few bargaining chips next.
不过首先
But first...
铁拳有个新盟友给他助拳
The Iron Fist has a new partner in his fight.
夜魔侠
Daredevil.
-太酷了  -这确实  挺酷的
- So cool. - I mean, it's... it's kind of cool.
我长话短说
I'm gonna make this real simple.
你乖乖回答我们的问题
You're gonna answer our questions
不然就让你生不如死
or shit's gonna get dark in here.
他们管你叫什么
What do they call you?
地狱厨房的恶魔
The Devil of Hell's Kitchen?
就算你能杀了我
Even if you could kill me,
也不会改变什么
it wouldn't make a difference.
切断一根手指  整只手还可以用
Cut off a finger... you can still use your hand.
我们一定会取胜  我们人多势众
We will win. We have armies.
我们有秘密武器
We have our weapon.
那就说说你们的武器  你们对她做了什么
Let's talk about your weapon. What did you do to her?
你们对艾丽卡做了什么
What did you do to Elektra?
艾丽卡
Elektra?
是
Yeah.
你们把她从坟墓里掘出来
You dug up her grave.
然后你们把她变成了什么
And what did you turn her into?
你认识的那个人不过是一具等待使用的驱壳
The body you knew was merely a vessel, waiting for its purpose.
她现在是我们的了
She's ours now.
既然她只是你们的躯壳
If she's your vessel...
那为什么她没杀了我
why hasn't she killed me yet?
有两次她都可以杀了我  但她没有
Twice now, she could've taken my life, but she hasn't.
你觉得原因是什么
Why do you think that is?
你们的武器有缺陷
Your weapon is defective.
那她就会被销毁
Then she will be destroyed.
有我在就休想
Not on my watch.
悠着点  弄死了就救不活了
Hey, stop. You can't undo this.
承认吧
Admit it.
艾丽卡还活着  你们失败了
Elektra's still in there. You failed.
失败的是你
You're the one who failed.
在那屋顶上  艾丽卡死在了你怀里
Elektra died on a rooftop in your arms
因为你没能保护她
because you couldn't protect her.
见鬼
Shit.
他死了吗
Is he dead?
很遗憾还没  昏过去了
Eh, unfortunately, no. Passed out.
该告诉他们真相了  小子
I think it's time to tell them the truth, kid.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
夜魔侠已经有一阵子没在这座城市活动了
Daredevil has not been active in this city for a while.
我亲眼看见的
I saw him with my own eyes.
这有什么要紧吗
Why is this a concern?
他确实武艺精湛  我们也不差
He's a skilled fighter, yes, but so are we.
我担心的不是和他对打
It is not his fighting that worries me.
而是他和艾丽卡·纳齐丝的关系
It is his relationship with Elektra Natchios.
她在上一世曾经与他并肩作战
She fought side by side with him in her last life.
不止如此
It is more than that.
他是她的爱人
He is the one she loved.
她攻击我的时候
When she attacked me...
我原本以为是不让我抢食
at first, I thought she was protecting her kill.
但你怀疑她是在保护他
But you think she was protecting him.
我不认为她如之前保证的那样
I do not think she is the empty vessel
只是一具躯壳
we were promised.
你之前想和我讨论的就是这个事吗
Is this what you wanted to discuss with me earlier?
你认为黑空辜负了我们的期望
You believe the Black Sky has failed us?
不是
No.
我认为是你
I believe you have.
你擅自作出决定
You made a unilateral decision
用尽了我们最后的资源复活了她
and used the last of the substance to resurrect her.
现在我们全都身处危险之中
And now, we are all vulnerable.
其实有她在我身边  我从没有这么安心过
Actually, I have never felt better than with her at my side.
只不过这不光是为了你
Except, it's not about you.
还有我们所有人
It's about us.
他说得对
He's right.
五指合而为手  我们合作才最强大
Five fingers created the Hand. We're stronger together.
现在只剩四个了  索旺达不在了
There are only four now. Sowande is gone.
-他会回来的  -这可说不准
- He will return. - You don't know that.
这是第一次  死亡成为了可能
For the first time, death is a possibility.
即便他回不来
Even if he doesn't,
我们也会活下去
we will survive.
只不过黑空
Except the Black Sky...
差点杀了我
almost killed me.
那样的话就只剩三个了
Then there would be three.
也许这正是我们需要的
Perhaps this is what we needed.
一个警醒  我们在座所有人并非不可或缺
A reminder that everyone in this room is expendable.
所有人
Everyone.
也包括你
Including you.
你似乎忘了我们发起这次任务的原因了
You seem to have forgotten why we started this mission.
忘了我们为什么需要铁拳
Why we need the Iron Fist.
不  我没忘
No, I haven't.
原因就是我们都想活下去
It's because we all want to live to see another day.
你是怕死了
You are afraid of dying.
而我们只想活到回家的日子
We want to live long enough to go home.
或许
Perhaps...
我们该考虑把黑空剔除出计划了
it's time to make a plan without the Black Sky.
或者剔除我们无畏的领袖
Or our fearless leader.
我愿意与你合作
I was willing to work with you.
但我怎么才能相信你
But how can I trust you?
她的名字是艾丽卡
Her name is Elektra.
她是他养大的  受训对抗手和会
She was raised by him. Trained to fight the Hand.
她也战斗了  和我一起
Which she did, with me.
直到他们相信
Until they convinced themselves
她另有他用  就杀了她
she could serve another purpose and killed her.
之前我看她可是活蹦乱跳的
She looked pretty alive back there.
我知道  但我亲眼看着他们...
I know, but I was there when they...
她就死在我的怀里
I was holding her when she died.
死的是艾丽卡
Elektra died.
和我们战斗的那个已经是别人了
That thing we've been fighting, it's something else.
她被复活了
She was resurrected.
对
Right.
你怎么能不告诉我们
How come you didn't tell us?
等等  你说"复活"是什么意思
Wait a minute. What do you mean, "resurrected"?
他的前女友
His ex-girlfriend.
现在他认为自己能拯救她
Now he thinks he can save her.
所以你就差点害死我们
That's why you nearly got us killed?
我呼唤她名字的时候  她有反应了
When I said her name, she recognized it.
她认得我
She knew me, alright?
他们在复活她的时候不管做了什么
I think whatever they did when they resurrected her,
我觉得我都能触到她的内心
I think I can get through to her.
先说清楚
Okay, to be clear,
"复活"这个词我们已经说了三次了
we've now used the word "resurrected" three times.
这就是他们的能耐
It's what they do.
我们都答应了要开诚布公  马特
We agreed to put everything on the table, Matt.
我们要想击败手和会  就必须得除掉她
If we're gonna defeat the Hand, we gotta take her out.
不行  棍叟  我绝不允许
No, Stick. I won't allow it.
你知道这些事对我们而言有多难相信吗
Do you know how hard this is for us to believe?
你们信不信都不重要  说到底
It doesn't matter what you believe, at the end of the day...
不管她是谁  她都是个问题
whatever she is, she's a problem.
-撒谎也是个问题  -我并不想骗你们
- Lying is a problem. - I didn't wanna lie.
-我只是想保护她  -我可不想
- I was trying to protect her. - Well, I'm not.
而现在我最关心的人
And right now the people I care about
被关在警察局里  就因为你
are held up in a precinct because you got me
要我保护你的老相识
protecting some woman you used to know.
别说得这么简单  卢克  我是想帮忙
Don't oversimplify it, Luke. I'm trying to help.
真相就是这么简单  默多克
The truth is simple, Murdock.
不许动
Don't move.
我们也不必互相欺骗了
Let's not kid each other.
这对我们每个人都是切身利益
This is personal for every one of us.
但现在铁拳在我手里
But now I have the Iron Fist.
手和会寻找的关键
The key to what the Hand seeks.
是我们活命  救赎的钥匙
The key to life, to our salvation.
战争结束了
The war is over.
还早呢
Not yet.
我的孩子
My child?
我要和你谈谈
I need a word.